{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "The MIME specification extends the email message format beyond plain text, enabling the transfer of graphics, audio, and video files over the Internet mail system. S/MIME is an enhanced version of the MIME protocol that enables email security features by providing encryption, authentication, message integrity, and other related services.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of a network protocol that enables secure file transfer over SSH?",
      "options": ["TFTP", "SFTP", "Telnet", "FTPS"],
      "correct_answers": ["SFTP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "SFTP is an extension of the FTP protocol that adds support for SSL/TLS encryption.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A type of cryptographic network protocol for secure data communication, remote command-line login, remote command execution, and other secure network services between two networked computers is known as:",
      "options": ["RDP", "SSH", "Telnet", "SCP"],
      "correct_answers": ["SSH"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a suite of protocols and technologies providing encryption, authentication, and data integrity for network traffic?",
      "options": ["TLS", "SSH", "IPsec", "VPN"],
      "correct_answers": ["IPsec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which part of IPsec provides authentication, integrity, and confidentiality?",
      "options": ["SPD", "PFS", "AH", "ESP"],
      "correct_answers": ["ESP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A system that uses a public network (such as the Internet) as a means for creating private encrypted connections between remote locations is referred to as:",
      "options": ["WWAN", "VPN", "PAN", "VLAN"],
      "correct_answers": ["VPN"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which protocol enables secure, real-time delivery of audio and video over an IP network?",
      "options": ["S/MIME", "RTP", "SIP", "SRTP"],
      "correct_answers": ["SRTP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "An encryption protocol primarily used in Wi-Fi networks implementing the WPA2 security standard is called:",
      "options": ["TKIP", "CCMP", "SSL", "IPsec"],
      "correct_answers": ["CCMP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A security protocol designed to improve the security of existing WEP implementations is known as:",
      "options": ["WPA2", "RC4", "CCMP", "TKIP"],
      "correct_answers": ["TKIP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refer(s) to deprecated/insecure encryption protocols and cryptographic hash functions? (Select all that apply)",
      "options": ["DES", "AES-256", "MD5", "ECC", "SHA-1", "SSL", "RC4"],
      "correct_answers": ["DES", "MD5", "SHA-1", "SSL", "RC4"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which cryptographic protocol is designed to provide secure communications over a computer network and is the successor to SSL?",
      "options": ["IPsec", "TLS", "AES", "CCMP"],
      "correct_answers": ["TLS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Examples of techniques used for encrypting information include symmetric encryption (also called public-key encryption) and asymmetric encryption (also called secret-key encryption, or session-key encryption).",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "In asymmetric encryption, any message encrypted with the use of a public key can only be decrypted by applying the same algorithm and a matching private key (and vice versa).",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the algorithms listed below are not symmetric ciphers? (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": ["AES", "DES", "DHE", "ECC", "IDEA", "RC4", "RSA"],
      "correct_answers": ["DHE", "ECC", "RSA"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following algorithms do(es) not fall into the category of asymmetric encryption? (Select all that apply)",
      "options": ["AES", "DES", "DHE", "ECC", "IDEA", "RC4", "RSA"],
      "correct_answers": ["AES", "DES", "IDEA", "RC4"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The term \"KEK\" refers to a type of cryptographic key often used in key management systems to add an additional layer of security when encrypting and decrypting other cryptographic keys.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a shared secret authentication method used in WPA, WPA2, and EAP?",
      "options": ["PSK", "802.1X", "SAE", "TKIP"],
      "correct_answers": ["PSK"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a protocol used to set up secure connections and exchange of cryptographic keys in IPsec VPNs?",
      "options": ["SSL", "IKE", "ESP", "DHE"],
      "correct_answers": ["IKE"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a key exchange protocol that generates temporary keys for each session, providing forward secrecy to protect past and future communications?",
      "options": ["PFS", "SHA", "PGP", "DHE"],
      "correct_answers": ["DHE"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a cryptographic key exchange protocol that leverages ECC for enhanced security and efficiency?",
      "options": ["IKE", "ECDHE", "DHE", "ECDSA"],
      "correct_answers": ["ECDHE"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a solution designed to strengthen the security of session keys?",
      "options": ["ECB", "PFS", "EFS", "PFX"],
      "correct_answers": ["PFS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a public-key cryptosystem used for digital signatures, secure key exchange, and encryption?",
      "options": ["ECC", "RSA", "PKI", "DSA"],
      "correct_answers": ["RSA"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which cryptographic solution would be best suited for low-power devices, such as IoT devices, embedded systems, and mobile devices?",
      "options": ["ECC", "DES", "RSA", "AES"],
      "correct_answers": ["ECC"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the cryptographic algorithms listed below is the least vulnerable to attacks?",
      "options": ["AES", "DES", "RC4", "3DES"],
      "correct_answers": ["AES"]
    }
  ]
}